normalboots.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy - NormalBoots

Normalboots.com Privacy Policy

Effective January 24, 2014:

Normalboots.com is an online service that allows the public to download and stream free videos and that allows its members to set up personal profiles. Normalboots.com can.

Normalboots.com does not sell personal information about its members to any third party, including but not limited to e-mail addresses and names.

Normalboots.com will not share any individual personal information with third parties except as required by law.

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, Normalboots.com may disclose personal information provided to it by its members or customers to appropriate third parties in order to: (x) comply with any court order or other legal obligation, (y) enforce or apply Normalboots.com’s Terms of Use, or (z) to protect the rights, property, or safety of Normalboots.com, our members, or others. Normalboots.com may disclose and transfer personal information provided to it by its members or customers to a buyer in the event of a sale of all or part of Normalboots.com’s business (whether by asset sale, merger, or otherwise) where customer information is part of the assets being transferred to the buyer. Normalboots.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to verify users and to provide basic information to other users. Members may provide additional information at their discretion such as media interests and personal biographies. Additional information is not required for membership to Normalboots.com. Any personal information entered into a Normalboots.com profile aside from e-mail address, password and zip code should be considered viewable by the general public. This information may be used by third parties outside of Normalboots.com’s control. Members may remove their information from the system at any time and Normalboots.com will not keep a member’s information for any longer than is necessary to provide its services.

Normalboots.com logs IP addresses of visiting users for statistical purposes and to maintain the integrity of our online gaming features and forums. IP’s are not shared with any third party.

From time to time, Normalboots.com may provide demographic and statistical information to prospective partners for the purposes of securing advertising and/or for general promotion of the website. This disclosure will not share any personal information of individual users but is intended to give a broad overview of Normalboots.com’s membership.

Normalboots.com uses cookies to store login information and to record settings to a user’s local computer. This stored data does not attempt to “mine” any other information from a user’s system or to collect information on sites outside the Normalboots.com family of websites.

Normalboots.com takes great care to protect its users personal information but cannot unconditionally guarantee the security of its database from outside attack or compromise.

Normalboots.com allows members to post URL’s that may take users to other websites. Normalboots.com can make no guarantees as to the Privacy Policies of these sites.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

Normalboots.com will update this Privacy Policy from time to time and alert users of the changes via the Normalboots.com online forum or alert system. It is the responsibility of the user to be aware of the current policy.

Questions about Normalboots.com’s privacy should be directed to: [operations@screenwavemedia.com](mailto:operations@screenwavemedia.com)

## 

More videos from screenwavemedia
